Did you have any idea that librarians would be, like, attacked?
No, for what?
I don't know. Between me and librarians, I don't know which I'm more surprised about getting attacked on my 2023 bingo card.
So Liberation Station Bookstore, North Carolina's first black-owned children's bookstore,
is relocating from downtown Raleigh less than a year after opening due to threats.
So the owner, Victoria Scott Miller of Liberation Station, she cited numerous threats as the reason for the move,
mentioning a particularly disturbing phone call that targeted her eldest son. Let's check her out.
I think it is the power and presence of seeing a black family unit doing this work, and I think that that's the threat.
Okay, so walk with me on this. When I see stuff like this happening, I'm just like,
how is there time to talk s*** about me when stuff like this is happening?
So what I mean by that, though, is because, like, this, to me, is where our publications can lean in and amplify,
and next thing you know, we have communities showing up to support.
But if we don't tell about these things, then community doesn't know.
What is the point of black media if we are not wrangling our community to support?
I honestly feel like that's the only purpose of black media.
It should be to amplify and to support.
Otherwise, I just, I'm like, what is, we have white media to do everything else.
Yep, yep.